realliving.com 2006-06-15

# Real Living - Buy a home. Sell your house. Find an agent and a mortgage.

### Our Committment to Privacy

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at  [customercare@realliving.com](mailto:customercare@realliving.com).

RealLiving.com understands and values the privacy of our consumers. We collect information from our Web site visitors in an effort to provide a Web site experience that is effective and efficient. In addition, we will use the information collected to notify you of changes to our site or services as well as communicating with you about products, services, contests and promotions. We recognize that we must use your information responsibly and maintain strict procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect all personal nonpublic information.

This Privacy Policy details the type of information we collect, the methods which we employ to collect the information, the reasons why we collect your information and how and when we share information. Also included in this policy is the process for your own management of your personal information.

Who is Real Living?   
Formed in January 2002, Real Living is more than 100 offices and nearly 5,000 associates. A network of leading residential real estate companies, Real Living offers buyers and sellers a variety of online tools that guide them through their buying and selling experiences. For more details,  [click here](http://www.realliving.com/AboutUs/0/History.aspx).

What kind of information RealLiving.com collects   
RealLiving.com may gather information in a variety of ways including loan applications, optional membership, voluntary surveys and other online forms requesting additional information about a property, product or service. Information collected may include name, email address, mailing address, telephone numbers. In addition, for certain request some financial details may need to be gathered including information regarding assets, employment and income, social security numbers and credit information. 

How RealLiving.com uses your information   
In some instances Real Living may share certain personal information regarding our customers. On occasion, Real Living may disclose some or all of your personal information to business partners or sponsors. Business partners may include but are not limited to insurance companies, home warranty partners, moving companies and other companies that provide services to home owners. In addition, many promotional offers may require that we collect and share certain personal information with outside vendors. 

Through our various partnerships, you may have the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you agree, Real Living will share any necessary personal, most often name and email address, with these third parties.

Use of IP Address   
Your IP address is a unique number used to identify your specific computer on a public network. Real Living may collect IP addresses for the purpose of system administration, to analyze consumer behavior and trends and to audit the use and functionality of our Web site. IP addresses are not linked to personal identifying information and are normally kept anonymous. Real Living may utilize an IP address to identify a Web site visitor when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site terms or to protect our service, site, consumers or others. 

Use of Cookies   
Real Living may use “cookies” to track the online behavior of our Web site visitors. Cookies are small amounts of data that the visitor retains on their computer. This process allows the visitor to go back to saved information from a previous visit. Cookies make web surfing easier for you by saving your preferences. Cookies do not tell us personal identifying information unless you have chosen to provide it to us. 

In addition to creating an easy web experience by saving your Web site preferences, Real Living may use cookies to track Web site usage trends and patterns. These usage patterns and trends may help us enhance the services we provide to our online consumer.

You have the option of disabling your cookies via your browser preferences.

Link to Web Sites and Services   
As a visitor of RealLiving.com, you should be aware that when you click on links that take you to a third-party Web site, you will be subject to their respective privacy policy. Real Living supports the privacy of all visitors to RealLiving.com but cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. It is important to read and understand the privacy policy of any Web site you may visit. 

Modifying Account Information and Opting Out   
You have the opportunity to ask us not to share information with third parties. In addition, we provide you with the opportunity to change or delete any personal information you may have provided to us. To make changes to your personal profile you may access this information by logging into MyRealLiving and clicking on your profile. In addition to changing or deleting information here, you may also opt-out and request that your personal information not be shared with third parties. You may also opt-out by emailing Customer Care at  [customercare@realliving.com](mailto:customercare@realliving.com).

Unsubscribing from all or select information   
To unsubscribe to email correspondence you can simply click on the link provided in each email or send an email to Customer Care at [ customercare@realliving.com](mailto:customercare@realliving.com).

How Our Policy is Monitored   
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact the Real Living Site Coordinator at [ customercare@realliving.com](mailto:customercare@realliving.com).

You will be notified should any changes or modifications be made to this policy and will have the option to opt-out based on applicable laws. Notices will be posted when you log into your account. Email notification may also follow when required.

Your acceptance of these terms: By using this site, you signify your agreement to Real Living’s Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE. Your continued use of Real Living and/or its affiliates’ sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

If you have questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at [ customercare@realliving.com](mailto:customercare@realliving.com).
